<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Pages on Operacastor Blog</title>
        <link>https://operacastor.github.io/en/page/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Pages on Operacastor Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>id-id</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://operacastor.github.io/en/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>About</title>
        <link>https://operacastor.github.io/en/about/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://operacastor.github.io/en/about/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello, my name is Operacastor and welcome to my blog.
This blog was created for various purposes, the first is as a place to document the output of my learning in the field of cybersecurity.
Second, I also use this blog as my digital portfolio.
Third, this blog is made for those of you who might want to learn more about cybersecurity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a random person, so it is very predictable that all posts on this blog will also seem random.
For friends who want to find my writings on a specific topic, then you should know that this blog has a search bar located on the &lt;strong&gt;Home&lt;/strong&gt; page.
So you can immediately search for posts that match what you are looking for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog is available in two languages, namely Bahasa Indonesia and English.
To change the language, you can select one of the language options at the bottom of the sidebar.
For those of you who use Bahasa Indonesia, there are some words in English that I didn&amp;rsquo;t translate into Bahasa Indonesia just to avoid confusion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So this is a brief explanation of this blog, hopefully this blog will be useful for all of us. That&amp;rsquo;s it, thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archives</title>
        <link>https://operacastor.github.io/en/archives/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://operacastor.github.io/en/archives/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Search</title>
        <link>https://operacastor.github.io/en/search/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://operacastor.github.io/en/search/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
